[EP03]
Young Marshal,
I'll get a doctor.
It's just a scratch.
It doesn't matter.
Lord Ling,
I found it.
It's the jade pendant of the Su family.
Bury my father's body here.
Keep it a secret.
Tell the outside
just say my father
has gone on a long journey
and hasn't returned yet.
Put everyone on high alert.
Keep a close eye on the Ye and Chu Families.
We can't afford any more trouble.
May I ask,
how should we
handle Miss Su?
The Sus killed the elder.
It's a done deal.
Miss Su has been poisoned by saxitoxin.
It's a lethal poison.
It can kill in seconds.
It's a miracle that she's still alive
until the doctor arrives.
She can't be disturbed.
Maybe she'll be safer in prison.
Let her mother stay with her.
Yes, sir.
Mom!
What's wrong with you, mom?
Don't leave me alone.
[The fire burned mom's face.]
My baby.
I'm here.
Mom.
I really miss you.
No.
She's not my mom.
I'm still in the novel.
Who are you?
[Is she Su Muwan's mother?]
Wan,
what's wrong with you?
Why don't you recognize me?
[Su Muwan's mother]
[has the same face as my mother.]
You suffered a lot.
Don't blame us.
Where am I?
What should I do?
This is prison.
It's Ling Shenxing
who put you in prison.
My father always told me to get rid of love
and lead the Ling family forward.
Now Mr. Su is dead,
and the Su's Trading Company has been closed.
There's no need for us to kill you.
As for Su Muwan,
she has no strategy,
and can't make a difference.
When the storm is over,
we can bring her back to the Ling family.
We found the body of the murderer outside the city.
After comparison,
it's the one who just assassinated you
on the way to the prison.
But it's totally different.
His hands were destroyed,
and we can't confirm his identity.
Miss Su
is placed in the prison.
It's not a good place,
but it's safe.
It's an emergency.
Miss Su should understand.
My child,
I'm so sorry.
I'll get you out of here.
Mom.
Maybe in this world,
we meet again in this way.
This is my mom.
Mom,
something happened to our family.
My good boy.
After your father disappeared,
the banned drug was found
in our granary.
Our business
was directly closed.
Our family
is ruined.
Master Su.
Mom doesn't know that dad is dead.
I have to hide it from her.
I can't let her be too sad.
Since we meet here,
I'll stay.
For you,
I'll get justice for the Su family.
The city
seems peaceful,
but it's not.
Mom,
what's the banned medicine?
There's no banned medicine.
Because of you,
we've been siding with the Lings
and staying neutral,
which made us a target.
They can't hurt the Lings,
so they
came after us.
But this has
nothing to do with you.
Your father and I
will handle it.
Mom,
I will never leave you or the Sus.
The ad is aired at this period of time.
Wait.
This feeling...
Mom,
have you been
insomniac lately?
Do you feel thirsty
and have palpitations at night?
Yes.
But Wan'er...
Mom,
what have you been eating lately?
This...
Tell me.
Who are you?
Stop.
Miss Su's servant Hongxiu
jumped over the wall and ran away.
Our people said
she sent a message
to Miss Su's brother,
Su Hong.
These days,
all the families are gathering information.
We can't make any more troubles.
What about Miss Ye?
As long as Su Mawan is there,
the Ye family will always have a target.
As long as Ye Jinrou is there,
the Ye family
will not arrange another pawn.
I'm not biased towards
either of the two of them.
After these days,
keep an eye on Su Muwan.
She can't beat the Ye family.
The prison is a bit poor,
but it's safe.
But how should we
deal with the relationship with the Su family?
Just let it be.
Young Marshal,
how about
getting someone to test the medicine first?
Your lives
are also important.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Mom.
Go.
Mu Wan.
Get up.
Go.
Wan.
Get up.
Mom.
Mom, get up.
You failed to protect her.
Go and take your punishment.
Yes, sir.
Please save my mom.
I beg you.
You don't even care about your own life.
How can you protect others?
She's my mom.
You are not Su Muwan.
Who are you?
Forget it.
You are not Su Muwan.
Who can you be?